http://www.moulding-warehouse.com/privacy/

Home
Products
Baseboards Casings Crown Moulding Top Caps | Headers Chair Rails Panel Moulding Baseblocks | Rosettes | Beadboards Door Hardware Door KnobsDeadboltsLeversHandlesetKeyless Door LocksDoor Hardware Door KnobsDeadboltsLeversHandlesetKeyless Door LocksDoor KnobsDeadboltsLeversHandlesetKeyless Door LocksDoor Hardware Door KnobsDeadboltsLeversHandlesetKeyless Door LocksDoor KnobsDeadboltsLeversHandlesetKeyless Door LocksDoor KnobsDeadboltsLeversHandlesetKeyless Door LocksDoor Hardware Door KnobsDeadboltsLeversHandlesetKeyless Door LocksDoor KnobsDeadboltsLeversHandlesetKeyless Door LocksDoor KnobsDeadboltsLeversHandlesetKeyless Door LocksDoor KnobsDeadboltsLeversHandlesetKeyless Door LocksDoor Hardware Door KnobsDeadboltsLeversHandlesetKeyless Door LocksDoor KnobsDeadboltsLeversHandlesetKeyless Door LocksDoor KnobsDeadboltsLeversHandlesetKeyless Door LocksDoor KnobsDeadboltsLeversHandlesetKeyless Door LocksDoor KnobsDeadboltsLeversHandlesetKeyless Door LocksDoor Hardware Accessories Columns Interior Doors
Suppliers
Moulding Warehouse Ltd.DorexCanaropaJeldwenLemieux Doors Inc.Trimlite DoorsWeiserTaymor
Moulding Ideas
Gallery
About Us
Moulding Warehouse Privacy Policy
At Moulding Warehouse, your privacy is very important to us.
Moulding Warehouse does not share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, or protect our rights.
Moulding Warehouse does not store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
Moulding Warehouse does not ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
Molding Warehouse Website Visitors
Moulding Warehouse Ltd., a leading supplier of prime MDF moldings, collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Moulding Warehouse’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our website visitors use the website.
Moulding Warehouse also collects potentially personally identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments or questions on our site. We do not share personal information collected to any source except as required by law, Homeland Security or Customs officers. Moulding Warehouse will not provide, sell or share any customer information to any other third party. All information is protected and not available to outside parties except as indicated above.
